So over the last lectures, over this module which was quite long, we built our first react application
Bu nedenle son dersler zerinde olduka uzun modl overdyes modunda olduka serin ve burada
which looks pretty cool and which works pretty awesome. Here
olduka harika alyor bizim ilk yeniden uygulama oluturduk.
we got a lot of features you learned about in the previous core sections. You learned how to plan your
nceki ekirdek blmlerde rendiiniz birok zellik var; uygulamanz bileenlere nasl bltnz
application, how to split it into components, how to have these components communicate with each other
nasl planlayacanz reneceksiniz Bu bileenlerin birbirleriyle nasl iletiim kuracaklarn nasl
via props, how to pass method references to components so that a click on the backdrop triggers a
reneceksiniz? Neden bileenlere yntem bavurularn nasl iletebileceiz? Arka zemin zerine tkladmzda, durumumdaki dzen
method in another component like in the layout component in our case,
bilgisayarnda olduu gibi baka bir bileendeki bir yntemi tetikler.
these are all core concepts of modern react applications. Being aware of how to communicate, how to structure
Bunlarn hepsi, modern yeniden hareketli uygulamalarn ekirdek kavramlar, bileenlerinin nasl oluturulacan ve
it, how to build the components and the pitfalls react offers.
geri getirilen tuzaklar nasl yaplandrlacann farkndadrlar.
Being aware of concepts like the auxiliary higher order components here or the shouldComponentUpdate
Buradaki yardmc yksek sipari bileenleri veya gmlek bileeni gncelleme mekanizmas gibi kavramlarn farknda olmak,
mechanism is crucial to building successful react apps.
baarl yeniden uygulama uygulamalar yapmak iin ok nemlidir.
Now we're not done at all,
imdi hi bitirmedik.
we'll dive much deeper into react, you will learn how to reach out to the web to save your data there
Verilerinizi oraya kaydetmek iin Web'e nasl ulaacanz reneceksiniz veya buradan getireceiniz
or fetch it from there, you will learn how to handle state in a better way, how to route, how to do a lot
ey, durumu daha iyi bir ekilde nasl ele alacanz reneceksiniz. Nasl yapacanz nasl ynlendireceinizi
of other awesome things with react.
nasl ynlendireceinizi. mthi eyleri tepki gsterdi.
But here you've got solid foundations and I can only encourage you to play around with this project,
ancak baz zellikler deien zelliklere sahipken, dier bileenlerle birlikte oynamay seviyorsanz
enhance it a little bit, add some features, change the styling, add other components, add more ingredients
burgere daha fazla katk maddesi ekleyerek biraz urak gibi ve tepki ile daha iyi olsun.
to the burger, whatever you like, play around with it and get better with react.
Ama salam temellere sahipsnz ve bu projeyle sizi oynamaya tevik eden,
Building projects is the best way of learning anything and that is of course also true for react therefore.
Bowling projeleri bir ey renmenin en iyi yoludur ve bu nedenle de yeniden hareket iin tabii ki dorudur.